<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="panelListHelp">
<![CDATA[
 <h1>HELP - List Panel Screen</h1>
 <p>
This screen displays list of players on the current panel.  The name of the panel is displayed
at the top of the screen. (If panel name is null use the the <b>rename panel</b> to assign
a name.)
 </p> 
 <p>
On startup for first time screen will be empty. Touch <b>+</b> to get started, you will be prompted to 
enter a Panel Name first and then the details of the first player on the panel<br/> 
 </p>
 <p>
Touch <b>+</b> to add additional players to the current panel<br/> 
 </p>
 <p>
Swipe up and down to scroll if list extends off end of screen
 </p>
  <p>
Touch on a<b> <i>player row</i> </b>to see and / or edit player details </p>
 <p>
<b>LongPress</b> a <b><i>player row</i></b> to get options to:<br/>
1. delete player<br/>
2. make phone call to player <br/>
3. send text to player<br/>
 </p> 
 <p>
<b>Drop Down Menu</b> <br/>
• <b>new panel</b> creates a new panel. Enter the name for the new panel. The existing panel will be saved and
can be returned to using the <b>change panel</b> option<br/>
• <b>change panel</b> changes to another previously entered panel. <br/>
• <b>rename panel</b> changes the name of a panel.  Select the panel you want to rename and enter a new name<br/>
• <b>delete panel</b> select panel to delete<br/>
• <b>import panel</b> load a saved panel from storage. You will need to have a file explorer APP 
(e.g. ES File Explorer) installed to list the available files. Note:
Panel files are stored by default in the <b>match_teams</b> directory on your devices External storage directory.
You can use a File Explorer App to view contents of <b>match_teams</b> directory<br/>
• <b>export panel</b> save the current panel to the device (panels are stored in a directory
 named match_teams)<br/>
 </p><br/>
 <p><b>Importing existing panels</b> <br/>
If you have an existing panel (in a spreadsheet for example), format it as a csv file and put in the match_teams
directory on your devices external storage to import it
 to the app.  The easist way to get the correct format is to examine an exported file.
 </p>
 
 <p>touch <b>back button</b> to return to previous screen.
 </p>
 ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="panelEditHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>HELP - Create / Edit Player Screen</h1>
<p>
Enter player details here.
</p>
<p>
You must enter a Nickname as a minimum to be able to Save a player.  
Other fields are optional. The Nickname must be between 3 and 6 characters long.
</p>
<p>
Touch <b>Save</b> to create a new player or save edits to an existing player.
</p>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="reviewListHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>HELP - Review Screens</h1>
<p>
View list of match statistics 
</p>
<p>
<b>LongPress</b> a <i>row</i> to get options to delete it<br/>
</p>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="trainingHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>HELP - Attendance Screen</h1>
<p>
Enter <i>date, location</i> and any <i>comments</i> here.
</p>
<p>
Touch the <b> select players present</b> button to display a list of players on 
the panel. Touch the <b>checkboxes</b> beside each player to record their attendance.
Swipe/Scroll to see full list if necessary. Click OK when finished.<br/><br/>
A list of selected players will be displayed on return.
<br/><br/>Touch the <b>select players present</b> button again to add or remove players
from the list
</p>
<p>
Touch <b>save players</b> to save the list of attending players to the database.
</p>
<p>
<b>Filters</b><br/>
Use filters to save and view attendance at specific events. So for example, create a 
<i><b>match</b></i> filter for matches, a <i><b>training</b></i> filter for training, <i><b>gym</b></i> 
for conditioning session etc.<br/>
When a filter is set and data is saved with the filter, the list of events and review attendance
sections will only display events for the set filter.<br/>
Reset to <i><b>No Filter</b></i> to see all events data 
</p>
<p>
Touch <b>review attendance by player</b> to get a summary of attendance for each player
at each training training session. Note that your device must be able to open csv files.
</p>
<p>
Touch <b>email attendance</b> to save and email the attendance summary.  The summary will be
saved and emailed as a csv file called <b>training_summary.csv</b>  
</p>
<p>
<b>list of training sessions</b> <br/>
Touch on a row/date to see details for that specific training session.  <br/>
Long press on a row/date to delete details of a specific training session.
</p>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="startHelp">
<![CDATA[
<p><b>Contact Details: <br/>
email:</b> gaaapps@gmail.com<br/>
<b>twitter: follow @gaaapps</b> for updates<br/>
If you are interested in a customised version or additional features 
or in training in how to use the App, please contact
email address.
</p>

 <p>This App allows you to:<br/>
	• to store contact details for a panel of players<br/>
	• to record attendance at training<br/>
 	• time and keep score for a football match<br/>
	 • record team and player performance statistics<br/>
	• review some summary statistics instantly<br/>
 	• save / share / email raw statistucs data in a csv format which can be opened in spreadsheet
 	software for more detailed analysis later<br/>
  </p>
  
 <p>It is recommended that you install the Twitter App and a File Explorer App
 (e.g. ES File Explorer) on your device to make use of all the features of this App<p>
 
 <p>Use the <b>manage panel</b> section to enter your team name and players.<br/>  Record and monitor
 attendance in the <b>manage attendance</b> section.<br/>  Long press on <b>start new match</b> to select a team
 lineup, time and record match stats, and to review stats for a new match.<br/> Click on
 <b>continue existing match</b> to return to details of an existing match. <br/>
 After a match is complete, click on <b>save/share match data</b> to save and share/email a full set
  of match events, scores, stats, team lineups.  This data can be opened as a spreadsheet for more
  detailed analysis subsequently.<br/>
  <b>setup</b> allows you to configure certain settings in the App and to configure custom
  statistics for your own use.<br/>
 
 
 <h1>HELP - Start Screen</h1>
 <p><b>help</b><br/> 
 	Touch <b>?</b> in menu bar at the top to get help in any screen.
 </p> 
 <p>
 <b>manage panel</b><br/> 
 	Touch to create and manage panels, players and contact details.
 </p>
 <p>
 <b>manage training</b><br/> 
 	Touch to record and display and share attendance at training / matches / events.
 </p>
 
 <p>
 <b>start new match</b><br/> 
 (you have to long press button to get this to work)<br/>
 	<b>NOTE:</b>All match related data - timer/scores/statistics -  is 
 	deleted/reset and a new match setup will begin.<br/>
 	Panel details and the team lineup from the previous match are retained.
 </p>
 <p>
 <b>continue existing match</b><br/> 
What it says!.  All current match data is retained.
 </p>
 <p>
 <b>save / share match data</b><br/> 
	match and statitics data for the current match is backed up to device storage and 
	can be shared/emailed.  <br/>
	Files stored/emailed are:<br/>
	• shots.csv <br/>
	• frees.csv <br/>
	• kickouts.csv <br/>
	• custom.csv <br/>
	• positions.csv <br/>
	The .csv files can be opened with spreadsheet software<br/>
 </p>
 
 <p>
 <b>setup</b><br/>
 In this section you can configure certain App settings and setup custom statistics recording<br/>
 There are 3 sections. In all 3, click on the text you want to edit and enter the new value. 
 When you are finished click <b>save all</b> to save all entries and quit.<br/>
 Click <b>quit</b> to exit without saving.<br/>
 Click <b>reset all to default</b> to reset all values to the original App default values.<br/><br/>
 
 </p>
 
 <p>
 <b>quit</b><br/>
 	 quit app. No data is deleted.
 </p>
<p><b>touch back button to return to previous screen.</b></p>
 ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="setupHelp">
<![CDATA[
 <h1>HELP - SETUP screen </h1>
 <p>
 This screen is used to enter match details, and make/save team selection.<br/><br/>
 By default, the team selection from the last match is retained so you can edit
 it rather than start from scratch. To clear the team selection long press the <b>
 reset team</b> button.
 </p>
 <p>
Enter <i><b>Date, Opposition Team name</i> and <i>Location</i></b> at top of the screen. Own team 
name defaults to the current panel name.  To change it go into the <b>manage panel</b> section.
</p>
 <p>
To select the team, touch on one of the position buttons.  This will display a list of 
players on your panel. Swipe/scroll, if necessary, to see all players and touch one to select.  
Repeat for all the positions<br/><br/>

It is not necessary to select a player for all or any of the positions, you can just leave the 
number if you prefer.
</p>

 <p>
Select <b>RESET POSITION TO NUMBER</b> to reset any position.<br/><br/> 
 </p> 
 <p>
If you need to enter new player names, use the <b>back</b> button to get out to 
the home menu screen and go into the <b>manage panel</b> section. When you have finished
entering new names touch <b> continue existing match </b> to continue setting up team.
 </p>
<p><b>swipe screen or touch tab at top to change to <b>RECORD</b> or <b>REVIEW</b> screens.</b></p>
<p><b>touch back button to return to Start screen.<b>
 ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="recordHelp">
<![CDATA[
 <h1>HELP - RECORD screen </h1>
 <p>
 <b>TIMER SECTION</b><br/>
 Touch the <b>mins/half</b> button to set how long the match will be. You can do this while
 the timer is running if you forget to do it at the start.<b/><br/>
 Touch the <b>start</b> button to start the match timer. Screen will update with start time, 
 time gone and time left in the half.<br/>
 You can touch the <b>-</b> and <b>+</b> to adjust the time by 30 secs if necessary while the timer
 is running.<br/>
 Touch <b>stop</b> to end the first half and <b>start</b> again to commence the second half.
 <br/><br/>
 Touching <b>stop</b> at the end of each half also saves the score and start times to the
 database.
 </p>  
 <p>
 <b>SCORE SECTION</b><br/>
 Touch the <b>goals</b> and <b>points</b> buttons to increment the scores.<br/>
 Touch the <b>-</b> and <b>+</b> buttons to decrement the scores.<br/>
 <p>  
 <p>
 <b>RESET SECTION</b><br/>
 Long touch to reset match <b>timer</b> and/or <b>score</b> and/or <b>stats</b>.
 </p>
 <p>
 <b>RECORD STATS SECTION</b><br/>
 In this section you can record info/statistics pertaining to shots, frees and kick outs
 for your own team and the opposition. Own team always refers to the team on the left
 of the screen<br/><br/>
 Touch the <b>shot / free / kick out / custom</b> buttons to record stats. <br/><br/>
 The five most recent stats entries recorded are displayed at bottom of screen. If you make a mistake,
 press <b>undo last stats entry</b> to delete the most recent entry and then reenter the stat <br/><br/>
 
 <b>1. Shots</b><br/>
 You can record:<br/>
 • shot outcome<br/>
 • shot type<br/>
 • for your own team, the player name who took shot<br/>
 • for opposition team, the player number who took shot<br/>
 • zone on pitch from where shot was taken. (Note your own goal is always at the 
 bottom of screen with  opposition on top.)
 
 <br/><br/> 
 <b>2. Frees</b><br/>
 You can record:<br/>
 • reason for free (note that these can be customised in the <b>setup</b> section.<br/>
  • zone on pitch where free was conceded<br/>
 
 • for your own team, which player, if applicable, was committed the foul.  <br/>
 • for opposition team, if applicable, which of your own players was responsible for winning the free<br/>
 <br/><br/>
 
 <b>3. Kick Outs</b><br/>
   You can record:<br/>
 • kick out outcome<br/>
  • zone on pitch where kick out was won or lost<br/>

 • for your own team, which player, if applicable, won or lost the kick out<br/>
 <br/><br/>

 <b>4. custom</b><br/>
   You can record custom stats / events:<br/>
 • custom stats/events can be configured in the <b>setup</b> section<br/>
 • which player is associated with the event/stat<br/>
  • zone on pitch where event/stat occured<br/>
 
 </p>
 
<p>
Touch <b>undo last stats entry</b> to delete the last stats entry if you made an error.
You can delete up to the 5 most recent entries.
</p>

<p><b>swipe screen or touch tabs at top to change to <b>SETUP</b> or <b>REVIEW</b> screens.</b></p>
<p><b>touch back button to return to Start screen.<b>
 ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="reviewHelp">
<![CDATA[
 <h1>HELP - REVIEW screen </h1>
  <p>
 The review screen presents a summary of recorded statistics for the current match. <br/> <br/>
 </p>
<p>
 The <b>shots by player, review shots, review frees, review kickouts</b> and <b>review custom</b> buttons display a detailed list
 of all data / statistics recorded.<br/>

<p><b>touch back button to return to Start screen.</b></p>
 

 ]]>
    </string>

</resources>